<post>
  <content>
    <image>https://geebamore.github.io/pexels-photo-3784324-min.jpeg</image>
    <heading>Disk Usage 100% fix !! Working Guide</heading>
    <date>- October 06, 2021</date>
    <body>Hello guys, hope everyone is doing great and all are leading a safe and healthy life. We  all might have noticed that sometimes the disk usage of our pc turned to 100% without even performing any task even though we are having a good configuration pc !!    In this blog I am going to share a few tips and tricks that helped me in solving this glitch. Hope you will enjoy reading this post and feel free to mention your thoughts and also please feel free to mention any tips which I might have missed out. Without further delay lets get into the topic. Check if disk usage is 100% !!</body>
    <ref>https://digidune.blogspot.com/2021/10/disk-usage-100-working-fix.html</ref>
  </content>
  <content>
    <image>https://geebamore.github.io/pexels-photo-327345-min.jpeg</image>
    <heading>Eliminate render blocking resources</heading>
    <date>- July 09, 2021</date>
    <body>Hello guys, this is my first post hope you will find this interesting and useful. Please drop your valuable questions or suggestion in the comment section. Without further delay let’s jump into the topic.   I assume most of you are familiar with website creation and deployment.   Let’s jump into the most vital portion that every website needs to satisfy for giving   the visitors a great experience. Yes, that is the site speed and it also helps in ranking too. </body>
    <ref>https://digidune.blogspot.com/2021/07/eliminaterenderblockingresources.html</ref>
  </content>
    <content>
    <image>https://geebamore.com/blog/img/email-marketing_1.jpg</image>
    <heading>Benefits of Email Marketing for Your Business</heading>
    <date>- September 29, 2023</date>
    <body>Email marketing remains a cornerstone of successful marketing strategies for businesses of all sizes. While social media and other digital channels have gained prominence, email marketing continues to deliver exceptional results and offers a host of benefits that are hard to ignore. In this post, we'll explore some of the key advantages of email marketing that make it an indispensable tool for businesses </body>
    <ref>https://geebamore.com/blog/benefits-of-email-marketing-for-your-business.html</ref>
  </content>
</post>
